<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on João G. Sousa</title><link>//www.jgsousa.com/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on João G. Sousa</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 14:56:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//www.jgsousa.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Managing multiple python versions with Homebrew and Poetry</title><link>//www.jgsousa.com/posts/homebrew-poetry-python-versions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 14:56:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.jgsousa.com/posts/homebrew-poetry-python-versions/</guid><description>tl;dr brew install python@&amp;lt;pythonversion&amp;gt; to install multiple python versions poetry env use &amp;lt;pythonversion&amp;gt; to create virtual environment direnv to automatically switch on entering directory I&amp;rsquo;ve always felt a bit hesitant to try out new tools for managing my python development environments. I had been safe and happy in the antiquated but efficient pip + virtualenv + pyenv world, and had been burned before when I dared adventure beyond the path of the tried and true of old.</description></item><item><title>Example</title><link>//www.jgsousa.com/posts/example/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 15:58:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>//www.jgsousa.com/posts/example/</guid><description>Arboris stabantque carbasa caelum rogantem invicti committitur Dici dea positos errat regina damno ferro Lorem markdownum; arces caede sub toto et ab Rhanisque modo temptata haesit cavo fluidos sors. Auro ingemuit, Aeginae gratesque nymphis ille suis; amorem! Pectus acceperat vires stabulorum Aeneaden arva spumantiaque Latio, sint tota aerata procul et longis me. Potest a flentem temptatos postquam, praefractam profugum.
Multorum dux urbem collocat incedit a turba ver seniles natis, pendat defecerat et discite fuerat erit per excipiuntur, arripit.</description></item></channel></rss>